The Seven Year Hitch is a romance, comedy, tv
movie film directed by Bradford May.
Jennifer and Kevin are childhood best friends who have lived
together, platonically, as adults for many years.
When Jennifer decides to marry her cheating, manipulative boyfriend, Bryce Kevin has to stop
the wedding to protect her from making, what he believes is, a terrible mistake.
With a little help from his brother and neighbor Kevin discovers that he and Jennifer are already legally married
due to common law, having lived together for seven years and, as such, Jennifer can not marry Bryce.
Jennifer, played by Natalie Hall.
Kevin, played by Darin Brooks.
Bryce, played by Ryan Doom.
Jeremy, played by John Sloan.
Mr. Henderson, played by George Wendt.
Mrs. Von Hoffman, played by Frances Fisher.
Will Smith is an American actor, rapper, and film producer.
His breakthrough came when he played a fictionalised version of himself in
the 1990s television sitcom The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air.
The role brought him international recognition and two Golden Globe Award
nominations for Best Actor – Television Series Musical or Comedy.
He also served as an executive producer on 24 episodes of the series.
Two years later, Smith made his film debut in the drama Where the Day
Takes You, where he appeared as a disabled homeless man.
In 1995, he starred as a police officer with Martin
Lawrence in Michael Bay's Bad Boys.
The following year, Smith appeared as a Marine Corps pilot with Jeff Goldblum
in Roland Emmerich's science fiction film Independence Day.
The film grossed over $817 million at the worldwide box
office and was the highest grossing of 1996.
In 1997, he starred as Agent J in the science fiction film Men in Black, a role he
reprised in its sequels Men in Black II (2002) and Men in Black 3 (2012).
Smith portrayed heavyweight boxer Muhammad Ali in the 2001 biopic Ali.
For his performance he was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Actor and
the Golden Globe Award for Best Actor – Motion Picture Drama.
In 2004, he appeared in the animated film Shark Tale,
and science fiction film I, Robot.
The following year he starred as a professional dating
consultant in the romantic comedy Hitch.
Smith's portrayal of entrepreneur and salesman Chris Gardner in the biopic The Pursuit of Happyness
(2006) received Academy Award and Golden Globe Award nominations for Best Actor.
In 2008, he played a vigilante superhero in Hancock.
While the film received mixed to negative reviews, it became his eighth consecutive to gross over $100
million at the North American box office and grossed a worldwide total of over $624 million.
In 2015, Smith portrayed Nigerian-American physician Bennet Omalu in the biopic
Concussion for which he garnered a nomination for a Golden Globe Award.
The following year, he appeared in the action film Suicide Squad, which
grossed over $745 million at the worldwide box office.
In 2019, Smith starred as the Genie in the live-action adaptation of
the 1992 animation film of the same name, Aladdin.
The film is his highest grossing, with a worldwide
box office total of over $1 billion.
In 2022, Smith won the Academy Award for Best Actor for his
performance as tennis coach Richard Williams in King Richard.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.